Guide to the Mulford Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- WRITINGS, 1852-(1880's) 1905; Series II; 5' 2 1/2 (13 BOXES)
  - Sermons
    - I Corin. 13.13 (2 copies), undated (Box 15, Folder 145)
    - I Corin. 15.26, 1861 (Box 15, Folder 145)
    - I Corin. 15.35, undated (Box 15, Folder 145)
    - II Corin. 9.6,7, undated (Box 15, Folder 146)
    - I Corin. 13.14, 1861 (Box 15, Folder 146)
    - Galatians 5.16,17 (2 copies), 1862 (Box 16, Folder 147)
    - Ephesians 1.23, 1871 (Box 16, Folder 148)
    - Ephesians 3.14, undated (Box 16, Folder 148)
    - Ephesians 4.15, undated (Box 16, Folder 148)
    - Ephesians 5.14, undated (Box 16, Folder 148)
    - Ephesians 5.15,16, 1862 (Box 16, Folder 148)
    - Ephesians 6.10 (2 copies), 1888 (Box 16, Folder 148)
    - Philippians 1.21, undated (Box 16, Folder 149)
    - Colossians 3.1(2 copies), 1885 (Box 16, Folder 150)
    - I Thess.4.3, 1861 (Box 16, Folder 151)
    - Hebrews 2.9, undated (Box 16, Folder 152)
    - Hebrews 3.6, undated (Box 16, Folder 152)
    - Hebrews 4.14, undated (Box 16, Folder 152)
    - Hebrews 10.7 (2 copies), 1862 (Box 16, Folder 152)
    - Hebrews 12.1-2 (2 copies) (Box 16, Folder 152)
    - I Peter 2.21, 1862 (Box 16, Folder 153)
    - I John 2.25 (2 copies), undated (Box 16, Folder 154)
    - I John 5.8 (2 copies), 1862 (Box 16, Folder 154)
    - Revelation 14.13 (2 copies), undated (Box 16, Folder 155)
    - Memorial - Walker, Sarah Miller, 1874 (Box 16, Folder 156)
- SUBJECT FILE, 1840, 1848-1849, 1890, 1896, 1900, 1967; Series III; 71/2" (2 boxes)
  The "Subject File" is arranged alphabetically by category; alphabetically within each category.
  - Biographical
    - "Elisha Mulford," by Horace E. Scudder, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Fragment on E. Mulford (unknown writer), undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Certificate
    - Membership, Daughters of the American Revolution, 1896 (Box 19)
      (see MG Common folio, No.35)
  - Circular
    - Child's Hospital and Dispensary, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Finances
    - Personal (Box 17, Folder 5-7)
  - Genealogy
    - Mulford Family, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Letter
    - Ministers of the Gospel in England and France [by E.M.], undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Stephens, Alexander H. (copy), undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Newsclippings
    - re: The Nation (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - re: The Republic of God (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - re: Concord School (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - "Story of Fishhook Mulford", 1967 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Photographs
    - Mulford, Samuel Buell, 1840 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Mulford, Silvanus S., 1848 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Program
    - Cortland Academy, 30th Anniversary, 1849 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Solicitation
    - Cambridge Public Library, 1890 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Robert College with autograph notes by E.M. (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Tributes and Obituaries
    - Mulford, Elisha (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Writings of Others
    - Roland J. Mulford: The Political Theories of Alexander Hamilton, 1903 (Box 18, Folder 22)